Guide to the Davenport College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1934-1973 Maintained by the Master
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Davenport College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1934-1973 maintained by the master
1931-1973
RU 872
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
40
(32 boxes)
The materials consist of student records maintained by the master of Davenport College, Yale University.
Davenport College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-F-2 (YRG 13-F-2), Records of the master of Davenport College
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See inventory for details
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of student records maintained by the master of Davenport College, Yale University
Biographical / Historical
The title "Master" for chief executive officers of residential colleges was changed to "Head of College" in April of 2016.
College students; Davenport College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Classes of 1934-1973, 1930-1973; Accession 2001-A-146
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
  - Classes of 1934 - 1942 (Box 1)
  - Classes of 1943 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1944
    - Ba - Ot (Box 2)
    - Pa-Z (Box 3)
  - Class of 1945w (Box 3)
  - Class of 1946 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1947 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1947m (Box 4)
  - Class of 1947 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1948 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1949, 1949m
    - AD - EM (Box 5)
    - FA - TA (Box 6)
    - TH - Z, miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Class of 1950
    - A - HO (Box 7)
    - HO - SI (Box 8)
    - SL - W (Box 9)
  - Class of 1951
    - AL - RO (Box 9)
    - ROU - Z and Stamm (Box 10)
  - Class of 1952
    - AB - LO (Box 10)
    - LU - WO (Box 11)
  - Class of 1953
    - AG - G (Box 11)
    - H - Z (Box 12)
  - Class of 1954
    - AC - C (Box 12)
    - D - Y (Box 13)
  - Class of 1955
    - AD - ME (Box 14)
    - MO - ZE (Box 15)
  - Class of 1956
    - AL - HO (Box 15)
    - HS - W (Box 16)
  - Class of 1957
    - BA - I (Box 16)
    - J - Z (Box 17)
  - Class of 1958
    - A -B (Box 17)
    - C - Z (Box 18)
  - Class of 1959
    - A -S (Box 19)
    - U - W (Box 20)
  - Class of 1960
    - A -S (Box 20)
    - T - Y (Box 21)
  - Class of 1961
    - A - M (Box 21)
    - T -Z (Box 22)
  - Class of 1962
    - A - N (Box 22)
    - O - Z (Box 23)
  - Class of 1963
    - A - R (Box 23)
    - S - Z (Box 24)
  - Class of 1964
    - A - R (Box 24)
    - S - Y (Box 25)
  - Class of 1965
    - A - R (Box 25)
    - S - W (Box 26)
  - Class of 1966
    - A -P (Box 26)
    - R - Y (Box 27)
  - Class of 1967
    - A - W (Box 27)
    - A -Z (Box 28)
  - Class of 1969
    - B - G (Box 28)
    - H - Y (Box 29)
  - Class of 1970
    - A -L (Box 29)
    - M - Y (Box 30)
  - Class of 1971
    - A - ST (Box 30)
    - ST - Z (Box 31)
  - Class of 1972 (Box 31)
  - Class of 1973
    - A -B (Box 31)
    - BI - Y (Box 32)